trafficsourcesreviews.com 2015-03-20

# Privacy « Traffic Sources Reviews

**Site Security**

The purchase area of our site is secure. This means that any information you send us is protected by encryption. Shopping with us is safe and secure so you have nothing to worry about. Your credit card security is our highest priority.

**Privacy Policy**

We are committed to protecting your privacy. We will only use the information that we collect about you lawfully (in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998).

**Demographic Data Collection**

We collect information about you for 2 reasons: firstly, to process your order and second, to provide you with the best possible service. We will not e-mail you in the future unless you have given us your consent. We will always give you the chance to unsubscribe from any marketing email from us or from any of our partner companies in the future.

**The type of information we will collect about you includes:**

  * Your name
  * Address
  * Phone number
  * Email address

**Your Credit Card Details**

Please note that we do not store credit card details nor do we share customer details with any 3rd parties. Orders are processed on this site using Paypal secure merchant services.

**We will never collect sensitive information about you without your explicit consent.**

The information we hold will be accurate and up to date. You can check the information that we hold about you by emailing us. If you find any inaccuracies we will delete or correct it promptly.

The personal information which we hold will be held securely in accordance with our internal security policy. If we intend to transfer your information outside the EEA (European Economic Area) we will always obtain your consent first.

## **Cookies**

We may use technology to track the patterns of behaviour of visitors to our site. This can include using a “cookie” which would be stored on your browser. You can usually modify your browser to prevent this happening. The information collected in this way can be used to identify you unless you modify your browser settings.

## **What we share with third parties**

**Analytic Cookies**

We use an analytics company (Google Analytics) on this website so that we can gain certain information to aid us in the marketing of this site. The analytics company drops cookies via our website and collects non-personally identifiable information about you. We can then access the analytical information and study the traffic that has come to our site. This helps us get a better understanding of how users access and use our site, so that we can help improve our site design and improve the users experience as our website evolves and grows.

Google stores the information collected by the cookie on its servers in the United States. We have no control over what third parties do with their cookies and related information. Google may transfer this information to other third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google’s behalf. By using the website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above.

If you would like to learn about how to reject or delete cookies by Google, please visit the following link: <http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacypolicy.html>

## **Social Network Cookies**

**Facebook**

This cookie is set by Facebook. It allows a visitor to “Like” pages from our website to their Facebook page. You can read more information relating to Facebook’s usage of cookies and their Privacy Policy here: <https://www.facebook.com/help/?page=176591669064814> and also [http://www.facebook.com/about/privacy](http://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/)

**Google +**

This cookie is set by Google. It allows a visitor to +1 pages from our website on their Google + page. Visit the following link to see the Google Privacy Policy and learn how to set your Google Ad Preferences: [http://www.google.com/policies/privacy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/)

**LinkedIn**

This cookie is set by LinkedIn. It allows a visitor to share content from our website on their LinkedIn page. Visit the following link to see the LinkedIn Privacy Policy : <http://www.linkedin.com/static?key=privacy_policy>

By agreeing to the terms of this privacy policy, you consent to the cookies referenced above being dropped onto your machine. If you have any questions/comments about privacy, you should [contact us](http://trafficsourcesreviews.com/contact-us/) us either by email, fax or post.
